Finding Aid for the Recordings of Evenings for New Music, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Service copy compact discs reformatted from reel to reel tapes, 1964-1980, I.; CD 1-139
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 144, December 11, 1976, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 121 Preservation copy on DVD 74 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 109-110)
    Performers: John Boudler, Donald Knaack, Gregory Ketchum, Timothy Leaphart, Robert Mahoney, percussion; Walter Gajewski, tape; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 8:16
    Work number: ENM144-04
    Co-ordinative systems no. 10 (1976)
    Performers: James Fulkerson, trombone; Walter Gajewski, tape
    Work number: ENM144-05
    Performers: Carol Plantamura, voice; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Suzanne Thomas, harp
    Duration: 21:20
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 146, February 13, 1977, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 122 Preservation copy on DVD 75 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 111)
    Work number: ENM146-01
    Lament on the death of proposition 15 (1976)
    Performers: Cheryl Gobbetti, Henrik Svitzer, flutes; Nora Post, oboe
    Duration: 9:35
    Work number: ENM146-02
    Nachtwandler (1901)
    Performers: Martha Herr-Hanneman, voice; Henrik Svitzer, flute; David Kuehn, trumpet; Jan Williams, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 3:33
    Work number: ENM146-03
    Take that (1972)
    Performers: Albert Furness, Gregory Ketchum, Timothy Leaphart, Daniel Mink, percussion; Jan Williams, conductor
    Work number: ENM146-04
    La Barbara, Joan, 1947-
    Circular song (1975)
    Performers: Joan LaBarbara, voice
    Duration: 7:35
    Work number: ENM146-05
    Chords and gongs (1976)
    Performers: Joan LaBarbara, voice; Jan Williams, percussion
    Work number: ENM146-06
    The Ides of March no. 5 (1976)
    Performers: Joan LaBarbara, voice; Nora Post, oboe; Jan Williams, percussion
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 147, March 19, 1977, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 123 Preservation copy on DVD 76 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 112)
    Work number: ENM147-01
    Until Spring, part II (1974)
    Performers: Morton Subotnick, tape
    Work number: ENM147-02
    Four butterflies
    Work number: ENM147-03
    Two life histories
    Performers: Paul Schmidt, voice; Morton Subotnick, clarinet; Walter Gajewski, tape
    Duration: 29:45
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 148, March 20, 1977, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 124 Preservation copy on DVD 77 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 113)
    Work number: ENM148-01
    Earls, Paul, 1934-
    Doppleganger (1976)
    Duration: 14:00
    Work number: ENM148-02
    Grauer, Victor
    Polyhyperchord (1977)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Nora Post, oboe; John Boudler, percussion; Steina Vasulka, violin; Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello; Walter Gajewski, tape; Holly Elam, lights
    Duration: 36:35
    Work number: ENM148-03
    Beckett, Samuel, 1906-1989
    Not I (1906)
    Performers: Elizabeth Hiller, actress; Charlotte Grantham, auditor; Jayne A. Lehston, director; Kenneth Crosby, technical direction and lighting
    Duration: 24:07
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 151, May 7, 1977, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 125 Preservation copy on DVD 78 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 114)
    Work number: ENM151-01
    Under the umbrella (1976)
    Performers: John Boudler, Albert Furness, Gregory Ketchum, Timothy Leaphart, Michael Pugliese, percussion
    Duration: 28:55
    Work number: ENM151-02
    Violets (1977)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Walter Gajewski, tape
    Duration: 6:37
    Work number: ENM151-03
    Berg, Gunnar, 1909-
    Filandre (1953)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Diane Melillo, violin
    Work number: ENM151-04
    Scelsi, Giacinto, 1905-1988
    Ygghur (1965)
    Performers: Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello
    Duration: 12:38
    Work number: ENM151-05
    Gajewski, Walter and Svitzer, Henrik, 1947-
    Flute from the hip (1977)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Walter Gajewski, live electronics and tape
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 152, October 15, 1977, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 126 Preservation copy on DVD 79 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 115)
    Work number: ENM152-01
    Credo in us (1942)
    Performers: John Boulder, Gregory Ketchum, Jan Williams, percussion; John Tilbury, piano
    Work number: ENM152-02
    Persiflage (1977)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Jan Williams, percussion; Lejaren Hiller, conductor
    Work number: ENM152-03
    Okanagon (1968)
    Performers: John Boulder, tam-tam; Jan Williams, harp; Joelle Leandre, doublebass
    Work number: ENM152-04
    Instruments III (1977)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 19:53
    Work number: ENM152-05
    Dmaathen (1976)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 10:24
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 155, December 4, 1977, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 127 Preservation copy on DVD 80 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 116)
    Work number: ENM155-01
    A Conversation with Morton Feldman and Toru Takemitsu
    Performers: Morton Feldman, Toru Takemitsu
    Work number: ENM155-02
    Voice (1971)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute
    Work number: ENM155-03
    Garden rain for brass ensemble (1974)
    Performers: Philip Christner, Martin Weimer, William Osgood, Alan Dusel, trumpets; Chris Kenner, French horn; George Kroetsch, Lou Osgood, Isaiah Cooper, Richard Bell, trombones; Phil Rehard, tuba; James Kasprowicz, conductor
    Work number: ENM155-04
    Eucalypts I (197-)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Mario Falcao, harp
    Duration: 7:55
    Work number: ENM155-05
    Stanza II (1971)
    Performers: Mario Falcao, harp; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 6:10
    Work number: ENM155-06
    Piano distance (1961)
    Performers: John Tilbury, piano
    Work number: ENM155-07
    For away (1973)
    Duration: 5:57
    Work number: ENM155-08
    Waves (1976)
    Performers: Gary Hatt, clarinet; Chris Kenner, French horn; George Kroetsch, Richard Bell, trombones; Gregory Ketchum, bass drum; James Kasprowicz, conductor
    Duration: 10:55
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 156, February 12, 1978, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 128-Reel 129 Preservation copy on DVD 81 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 117-118)
    Work number: ENM156-01
    Hymnos (1967)
    Performers: Gary Hatt, clarinet; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 11:38
    Work number: ENM156-02
    In woods (1978)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Jan Williams, percussion; Mario Falcao, harp
    Duration: 27:08
    Work number: ENM156-03
    Syntagm III (1970)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Jan Williams, Gregory Ketchum, percussion; Krzysztof Knittel, piano; Mario Falcao, harp; Weronika Knittel, violin; Michael Peebles, violoncello
    Duration: 11:05
    Work number: ENM156-04
    Rucke di Guck (1955)
    Performers: Robert Dick, piccolo; Nora Post, oboe
    Duration: 8:40
    Work number: ENM156-05
    "... From behind the unreasoning mask" (1975)
    Performers: James Kasprowicz, trombone; Jan Williams, Gregory Ketchum, percussion; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 17:00
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 159, April 5, 1978, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 130-Reel 131 Preservation copy on DVD 82 Performed at Carnegie Recital Hall (Box 3, Cd 119-120)
    Work number: ENM159-01
    Williams, Neal
    To the sea in the whispering dark (1977)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Michael Peebles, violoncello; Gregory Ketchum, percussion
    Duration: 17:28
    Work number: ENM159-02
    Drummond, Dean, 1949-
    Zurrjir (1976)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Krzysztof Knittel, piano; Gregory Ketchum, Albert Furness, Michael Pugliese, percussion; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 5:52
    Work number: ENM159-03
    King, John, 1953 Nov. 28-
    Piano trio #1 (1977)
    Performers: Weronika Knittel, violin; Michael Peebles, violoncello; Krzysztof Knittel, piano
    Duration: 11:58
    Work number: ENM159-04
    Tenney, James
    Three pieces for drum quartet (1974-75)
    Performers: Gregory Ketchum, Albert Furness, Robert Mahoney, Michael Pugliese, percussion; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 16:35
    Work number: ENM159-05
    Johnson, Tom, 1939-
    Risk nine
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; James Tenney, piano; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 47:45
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 160, May 7, 1978, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 132 Preservation copy on DVD 83 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 121)
    Work number: ENM160-01
    Monochromie (1964)
    Work number: ENM160-02
    Spring music (1978)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Krzysztof Knittel, synthesizer; Weronika Knittel, violin
    Duration: 12:11
    Work number: ENM160-03
    Music for six (1977)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Jan Williams, percussion; Krzysztof Knittel, piano; Weronika Knittel, violin; Michael Peebles, violoncello
    Duration: 18:23
    Work number: ENM160-04
    Dick, Robert, 1950-
    Afterlight (1973)
    Duration: 5:38
    Work number: ENM160-05
    Standing (1973)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Gregory Ketchum, percussion; Weronika Knittel, violin
    Work number: ENM160-06
    Luster gave her hat and he and Ben went across on the backyard (1975)
    Performers: Gregory Ketchum, Albert Furness, Michael Pugliese, marimbas
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 161, October 28, 1978, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 133 Preservation copy on DVD 84 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 122-123)
    Work number: ENM161-01
    String trio, op. 45 (1946)
    Performers: Weronika Knittel, violin; Richard Field, viola; Ken Ishii, violoncello
    Duration: 17:32
    Work number: ENM161-02
    Kammerkonzert (1925)
    Performers: Laurence Trott, piccolo; Eberhard Blum, flute; Rodney Pierce, oboe; Florence Myers, English horn; Gary Hatt, E♭ clarinet; James Pyne, A clarinet, Allen Sigel, B♭ bass clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Ronald Daniels, contrabassoon; David Kuehn, trumpet; Duane Saetveit, Lowell Shaw, French horn; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Weronika Knittel, violin; Ursula Oppens, piano; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 32:13
    Work number: ENM161-03
    Kraft, William
    Des Imagistes (1974)
    Performers: Elizabeth Hiller, Saul Elkin, reciters; James Hayes, Bruce Penner, Walter Hunt, Michael Pugliese, Robert Mahoney, Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 23:05
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 162, December 16, 1978, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 134 Preservation copy on DVD 85 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 124-125)
    Work number: ENM162-01
    String trio, op. 20 (1927)
    Performers: Weronika Knittel, violin; Pamela B. Adelstein, viola; Ken Ishii, violoncello
    Duration: 9:42
    Work number: ENM162-02
    Osborne, Nigel
    Remembering Esenin (1974)
    Performers: Ken Ishii, violoncello; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 15:20
    Work number: ENM162-03
    Hachimura, Yoshio, 1938-
    Constellation (1968-69)
    Performers: Weronika Knittel, violin; Jan Williams, tubular bells; Michael Pugliese, vibraphone; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 15:48
    Work number: ENM162-04
    Waddington, Maurice
    Mehr Licht (1977)
    Duration: 11:25
    Work number: ENM162-05
    Linea (1974)
    Performers: Bruce Penner, vibraphone; Jan Williams, marimba; Ursula Oppens, Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 163, February 11, 1979, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 135 Preservation copy on DVD 86 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 126)
    Work number: ENM163-01
    Phantasy for violin and piano, op, 47 (1949)
    Work number: ENM163-02
    Sonatina for flute and piano (1946)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Stephen Manes, piano
    Work number: ENM163-03
    Improvisations sur Mallarme, I. Le Vierge, Le Vivace et Le Bel Aujourd'hui(1958-60); II. Une Dentelle S'abolit (1958)
    Performers: Phyllis Bryn-Julson, soprano; Stephen Manes, piano; Yvar Mikhashoff, celesta; Mario Falcao, harp; Michael Pugliese, Bruce Penner, vibraphone; James Hayes, chimes; Bruce Penner, Michael Pugliese, Robert Mahoney, Edward Folger, Walter Hunt, percussion; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 12:10
    Work number: ENM163-04
    "If you're so smart, why aren't you rich?" (1978)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, violin; Daniel Wittmer, Lori Noody, French horn; Charles Lirette, Philip Christner, Geoffrey Brown, Christopher Conlon, trumpets; James Kasprowicz, Thomas Miller, trombones; Don Harry, tuba; Akram, piano; Michael Pugliese, Edward Folger, chimes; Paul Schmidt, Thomas Sperl, doublebass, Julius Eastman, conductor
    Duration: 24:33
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 164, March 18, 1979, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 136 Preservation copy on DVD 87 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 127)
    Work number: ENM164-01
    Performers: Deborah Ungaro, clarinet; Kieko Yamazaki, violin; James Tenney, piano
    Duration: 5:28
    Work number: ENM164-02
    From the steeples and the mountains (1901)
    Performers: Geoffrey Brown, Philip Christner, Mitchell Robinson, trumpets; Craig Brown, James Kasprowicz, Thomas Miller, trombones, Walter Hunt, Edward Folger, Robert Mahoney, Michael Pugliese, bells; James Tenney, conductor
    Duration: 4:12
    Work number: ENM164-03
    Tone roads #1 (1911)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Deborah Ungaro, clarinet; Susan Huber, bassoon; Arne Almquist, Deborah Weiss, violin; Joanne Lowe, viola; Ken Ishii, Farley Pierce, violoncello; Thomas Sperl, doublebass; James Tenney, conductor
    Duration: 3:40
    Work number: ENM164-04
    Tone roads #3 (1915)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Deborah Ungaro, clarinet; Geoffrey Brown, trumpet; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Edward Folger, Michael Pugliese, chimes; Charles Clifton, piano; Arne Almquist, Deborah Weiss, violin; Joanne Lowe, viola; Ken Ishii, Farley Pierce, violoncello; Thomas Sperl, doublebass; James Tenney, conductor
    Duration: 3:24
    Work number: ENM164-05
    Scherzo: Over the pavements (1906-13)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Deborah Ungaro, clarinet; Susan Huber, bassoon; Mitchell Robinson, trumpet; Craig Brown, James Kasprowicz, Thomas Miller, trombones; Michael Pugliese, percussion; Charles Clifton, piano; James Tenney, conductor
    Work number: ENM164-06
    Angels (1921)
    Performers: Geoffrey Brown, Philip Christner, Christopher Conlon, Mitchell Robinson, trumpets; Craig Brown, James Kasprowicz, Thomas Miller, trombones; James Tenney, conductor
    Duration: 2:38:00
    Work number: ENM164-07
    Seeds I-VI (1956-61)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Deborah Ungaro, clarinet; Susan Huber, bassoon; Daniel Wittmer, French horn; Keiko Yamazaki, violin; Ken Ishii, violoncello; James Tenney, conductor
    Duration: 7:07
    Work number: ENM164-08
    Harmonium #5 (1978)
    Performers: Keiko Yamazaki, violin; Joanne Lowe, viola; Ken Ishii, violoncello
    Duration: 6:29
    Work number: ENM164-09
    Integrales (1926)
    Performers: Robert Dick, Susan Lutsky, piccolo; Stephen Beamish, oboe; Kyle Peterson, Deborah Ungaro, clarinet; Daniel Wittmer, French horn; Philip Christner, Christopher Conlon, trumpets; James Kasprowicz, tenor trombone; Craig Brown, bass trombone; Mark Jones, contrabass trombone; Walter Hunt, Edward Folger, Robert Mahoney, Michael Pugliese, percussion; James Tenney, conductor
    Duration: 10:57
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 165, April 29, 1979, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 137 Preservation copy on DVD 88 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 4, Cd 128-129)
    Work number: ENM165-01
    Hatzis, Christos, 1953-
    Cain (1978)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 19:27
    Work number: ENM165-02
    Picker, Tobias, 1954-
    Rhapsody (1978)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, violin; Tobias Picker, piano
    Duration: 12:40
    Work number: ENM165-03
    Alchemies (1979)
    Duration: 6:04
    Work number: ENM165-04
    Sequenza IX (1975)
    Duration: 16:10
    Work number: ENM165-05
    Scherzi (1974)
    Performers: James East, clarinet; Weronika Knittel, violin; Ken Ishii, violoncello; Claudia Hoca, piano
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 167, October 14, 1979, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 138 Preservation copy on DVD 89 Performed at University at Buffalo, Center Theatre (Box 4, Cd 130)
    Work number: ENM167-01
    Duo, violin and piano
    Performers: Paul Zukofsky, violin; Ursula Oppens, piano
    Duration: Not recorded
    Work number: ENM167-02
    Sonata, piano
    Performers: Paul Jacobs, piano
    Duration: 22:51
    Work number: ENM167-03
    Sonata, violoncello, piano
    Performers: Fred Sherry, violoncello; Ursula Oppens, piano
    Duration: 20:45
    Work number: ENM167-04
    Double concerto (1961)
    Performers: Ursula Oppens, piano; Paul Jacobs, harpsichord; Robert Dick, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Duane Saetveit, Mary Hunt, French horn; David Kuehn, trumpet; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Edward Folger, Walter Hunt, Bruce Penner, Glen Stern, percussion; Douglas Cone, violin; Diane Williams, viola; Takeshi Mineta, violoncello; Makoto Michii, double bass
    Duration: 22:49
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 168, November 18, 1979, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 139-Reel 140 Preservation copy on DVD 90 Performed at University at Buffalo, Baird Hall (North Campus) (Box 4, Cd 131-132)
    Work number: ENM168-01
    Hyxos (1961)
    Performers: Robert Dick, alto flute; Jan Williams, gongs
    Duration: 11:35
    Work number: ENM168-02
    Bryce (1976)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Mario Falcao, Suzanne Thomas, harps; Bruce Penner, Glen Stern, percussion
    Work number: ENM168-03
    Piano (1977)
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 30:25
    Work number: ENM168-04
    Parallel lines (1979)
    Performers: Laurence Trott, piccolo; Ronald Richards, oboe; Deborah Ungaro, bass clarinet; Bruce Penner, Glen Stern, percussion; Mario Falcao, harp; Diane Williams, viola; Mary Sue Wells, violoncello
    Duration: 15:36
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 169, December 10, 1979, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 140 Preservation copy on DVD 91 Performed at University at Buffalo, Baird Hall (North Campus) (Box 4, Cd 133)
    Work number: ENM169-01
    Sequenza V (1966)
    Work number: ENM169-02
    Exchanges (1973)
    Duration: 8:36
    Work number: ENM169-03
    Vorstellung (1977)
    Work number: ENM169-04
    Der Atem (1965)
    Work number: ENM169-05
    RES / AS / EX / INS-PIRER (1973)
    Duration: 11:07
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 170, February 24, 1980, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 141 Preservation copy on DVD 92 Performed at University at Buffalo, Baird Hall (North Campus) (Box 4, Cd 134-135)
    Work number: ENM170-01
    3 Gymnopodies (1888)
    Performers: Aki Takahashi, piano
    Duration: 10:00
    Work number: ENM170-02
    Ishii, Maki
    Black Intension III (1977)
    Performers: Aki Takahaski, piano
    Duration: 9:45
    Work number: ENM170-03
    Evryali (1973)
    Duration: 8:58
    Work number: ENM170-04
    Mode de Valeurs et d'intensities (1949)
    Duration: 3:37
    Work number: ENM170-05
    5 Nocturnes (1919)
    Duration: 14:53
    Work number: ENM170-06
    Suite No. 10 KA (1953)
    Work number: ENM170-07
    Je te veux (1900)
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 171, February 29, 1980, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 142 Preservation copy on DVD 93 Performed at University at Buffalo, Baird Hall (North Campus) (Box 4, Cd 136)
    Work number: ENM171-01
    Morris, Robert, 1943-
    Either ether (1978)
    Duration: 19:00
    Work number: ENM171-02
    Raudra (1976)
    Duration: 2:48
    Work number: ENM171-03
    Ghost Dances (1980)
    Performers: Robert Dick, piccolo flute, alto flute, bass flute
    Duration: 5:48
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 173, April 18, 1980, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 145 Preservation copy on DVD 94 Performed at University at Buffalo, Baird Hall (North Campus) (Box 4, Cd 137)
    Work number: ENM173-01
    Monument/Selbsportant/Bewegung fur zwei Klaviere (1976)
    Performers: Aki Takahashi, Ursula Oppens, pianos
    Work number: ENM173-02
    Vision de l'Amen (1943)
    Duration: 48:25
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 174, December 10, 1975, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 149 Preservation copy on DVD 95 Performed at WBAi Free Music Store (Box 4, Cd 138)
    Work number: ENM174-01
    Work number: ENM174-02
    Orchestral etudes. Three processes on nine sets (1975)
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 175, December 11, 1974, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 150 Preservation copy on DVD 96 Performed at WBAi Free Music Store (Box 4, Cd 139)
    Work number: ENM175-01
    Duration: ca. 60:00
- Reel to reel tapes not reformatted 1964-1978, II.; Reel 151-162
  Twelve tapes discovered and identified as containing Evenings for New Music content after the original reformatting project was completed. Some of the tapes contain concerts that were reformatted using the cassette copies that had been made for the Music Library. Other recordings are from WBAI concerts.
  Arranged in chronological order of concerts.concerts. Arranged
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 1, November 29, 1964, 3 7-inch reels; Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery The order of the last two works is reversed on the container. (Reel 151-153)
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 3: Partial copy, January 10, 1965, 2 7-inch reels; Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery The first and third works on the program of Concert 3 are not included in the labeling on the container. (Reel 154-155)
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 5: Partial copy, March 4, 1965, 1 7-inch reel; Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery This originally tape 3 of 3. The first two tapes have not been found. The remainder of the program of Concert 5 is available above. (Reel 156)
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 6: Partial copy, March 5, 1965, 1 7-inch reel; Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery This is tape 3 of 3. The first two tapes have not been found. The remainder of the program of Concert 6 is available above. (Reel 157)
  - Evenings for New Music Concert at WBAI Free Music Store, December 11, 1974, 1 7-inch reel; WBAI Free Music Store Label on reel: "CA Concert Dub 1st half Dec. 11 1974". The date matches that of an Evenings for New Music concert presented at WBAI Free Music Store. It is not clear what works are included. The content description consists of the first two works on the program before intermission. It is taken from a program for the WBAI concert. Presumably the last work on the program, Alvin Lucier's Still and moving lines of silence in families of hyperbolas is not on the tape. (Reel 158)
  - Evenings for New Music Concert at WBAI Free Music Store, October 28 1976, 2 7-inch reels; There is no program accompanying the tapes. Content description is from an original program in the Archive for the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts. The content cannot be confirmed until the tapes are reformatted. (Reel 159-160)
    Fusain: for flute alone
    Also performed on Evenings for New Music Concert 148, March 20 1977.
    Riley, Howard
    Improvisation for piano
    Performers: Howard Riley, piano
    Psappha